(upbeat music)
Satoru, show him
to his dorm room.
Be sure to explain the security
arrangements to him as well.
You're admitted,
welcome to Jujutsu Tech.
[Yuuji] Hey, Fushiguro!
Wow, you look all better now.
There's lots of other
empty rooms, you know?
Sure, but isn't it better
to have some company?
I thought it'd be good for--
Classes and the
missions are enough.
This is not welcome.
Whoa-oah, it's so
organized in here.
Back off.
I just told you
you're not welcome!
Huh, friends already
and together, we're
heading out tomorrow.
We're gonna go pick up
the third and final first year.
(whistle blows)
[Announcer] The train bound
for Shibuya and Shinagawa
is now arriving on track one.
For your safety, please
stand behind the yellow line.
[Nobara] Saori,
I'm finally here.
I'm in Tokyo.
How are there only
three first years?
That's practically nothing.
Think about it.
Can you honestly say
you've ever met someone else
who sees curses?
Huh, I guess not.
Because jujutsu
sorcerers, they're rare.
[Yuuji] Didn't you say I
was the third first year?
[Fushiguro] The others
admission was decided a while ago.
You know what
our school is like.
Everyone has
unique circumstances.
Sorry for the wait.
Oh, your uniform
made it in time.
Yeah, it fits great.
Though I noticed it's slightly
different from Fushiguro's.
Mine has got a hood.
[Gojou] That's
because the uniforms
can be customized upon request.
Huh?
But I never put in any requests.
You're right, I was the one
who put in the custom order.
Huh.
Oh, well cool.
Be careful, Gojou has a habit
of doing that kind of stuff.
So why are we meeting
up here in Harajuku?
[Gojou] Because that's
what she asked for.
[Yuuji] Yay popcorn,
I want some!
Why hello there.
Are you on the clock right now?
[Woman] No, not right now.
That's great, you see,
I'm looking for
potential models.
That's what I do.
Would you be interested?
[Woman] I'm in
a hurry right now.
[Talent Scout] Wait,
just hear me out.
Hey you, what about me?
[Talent Scout] Oh boy, her?
For that modeling gig.
Hey, I'm asking what
you think about me.
Oh well, I'm in a
hurry at the moment.
What the hell?
Don't run, come out
and say what you think!
Wait, she's the one we
have to go and talk to?
This is real embarrassing.
(scoffs) Yeah, so are you.
Hey, we're over here!
[Girl] Oh damn, what's
up with that blindfold?
Right, I'd like you to meet...
Nobara Kugisaki.
You should be honored, boys.
I'm your group's girl.
(Opening Theme Music)
(singing in Japanese)
Stare...
I'm Yuuji Itadori from Sendai.
Fushiguro.
He looks like a potato.
He's definitely the type that
ate his own boogers as a kid.
And just his name?
I can't stand
high-and-mighty dudes.
I bet he likes setting
oil-slicked seagulls on fire.
(groans) This is what
I get to work with?
Great, just my luck.
She took one look and sighed.
That can't be good.
Are we going
somewhere from here?
(chuckles) Well we do have
all three of you together.
And since two of you kids
are from the countryside,
that means we're going to Tokyo!
[All] Tokyo! Tokyo!
Tokyo!
[Both] We love Tokyo!
-Huh?
-TDL!
I want to go to TDL!
Idiot! TDL's in Chiba!
Let's go hit up
Chinatown instead!
Chinatown's in Yokohama, dummy!
Well Yokohama's part of Tokyo!
How do you not know
that? Look at a map!
If you quiet down, I'll
announce our destination.
Roppongi!
[Both] Roppongi?
[Fushiguro]
There's a curse here.
-You liar!
-This isn't Roppongi!
-It's a cruel move
to toy with country folk!
[Gojou] There's a
big cemetery nearby.
That, plus an
abandoned building,
and you've got a curse.
So they pop up more
often around graves.
Huh?
It's not the cemetery itself.
It's the fact that people
associate cemeteries
with fear and uneasiness.
Right, it was the same
for schools, too, wasn't it?
Wait hold up here.
He didn't even know that yet?
To be honest...
(gulps)
He swallowed a
special-grade cursed object?
Gross!
That's so unsanitary and
disgusting I wanna hurl.
No way, no way, no way!
That's not nice.
I agree with her.
I want to know what the
three of you are capable of.
Just think of this as
a kind of field test.
Nobara, Yuuji,
you go exorcize the
curse inside that building.
(Nobara grunts)
Hold on.
I thought only curses
could exorcize curses.
I can't use jujutsu yet.
If you look at it, you're
basically half a curse already.
Cursed energy flows
through your body.
Although, controlling
that energy
isn't something you
can learn overnight.
So you use this.
The Slaughter Demon.
A weapon imbued
with cursed energy.
So it'll work on curses too.
Ugh, how lame.
[Gojou] Oh, one more thing.
-Huh?
-Don't let Sukuna out, okay?
If you use him, you'll get
rid of all curses in that radius,
but anyone nearby
will get dragged in.
You got it. I won't let him out.
(Nobara grunts)
Would you hurry it up?
-All right, all right.
-Have fun!
(door creaking)
I think I'll go in too.
Don't push yourself.
You're still
recovering, you know.
[Fushiguro] But someone
needs to keep an eye
on Itadori, right?
[Gojou] True.
But the one we're testing
this time around is Nobara.
What a pain in my ass.
I come all the way to Tokyo
and I still have to
deal with dumb curses.
Huh?
You didn't come
here to exorcize them?
Let's save some time.
You and I should split up.
I'll start from the top and
investigate floor by floor.
You start from the bottom.
Let's knock this out and
grab some sushi in Ginza.
Hold on a minute.
Let's take this seriously.
Curses are dangerous, you know.
(Nobara grunting)
(Yuuji screams)
I don't wanna hear
it from someone
who last week was
a clueless normie!
Now get moving! (grunts)
You're an out of control roller
coaster of emotions today!
[Nobara] This is why
girls don't like you!
How do you know
they don't like me, huh?
Are you even popular
enough to talk?
Bitch.
Huh?
(splashing)
(upbeat music)
Do you need a receipt?
It's a curse!
(curse warbling)
(screaming)
(grunting)
Hmm-mm.
Have I got moves or what?
(guts splashing)
That Yuuji.
Some screws are loose.
He's fearless.
These things take the
form of terrifying creatures
and try to kill him.
Yet the guy has
no hesitation at all.
And he doesn't
have the familiarity
with curses that you have.
We're talking about a boy
who used to live a
normal high school life.
By now, you've seen
plenty of jujutsu sorcerers,
some talented.
And you've seen them give up
'cause they couldn't conquer
their fear or disgust, right?
So today's about seeing if
she's crazy enough for this.
(sighs) Hey. Whaddup, curse?
Yeah you, mannequin
in the center.
You actually think
you're hidden there?
Fine then.
I'll do this from here.
But Kugisaki has
experience, right?
So it's a little
late for that now.
As we know, curses are
born from human minds.
So their strength and numbers
grow in proportion
to the population.
(light upbeat music)
(Nobara grunts)
Do you think Nobara understands
Tokyo curses are
on a different level
than those in the countryside?
(upbeat music)
Curses are born
from human minds.
So their strength and numbers
grow in proportion
to the population.
Tokyo curses are
on a different level
than those in the countryside.
You know, you might
wanna pull those out,
(snaps fingers)
or my cursed energy
will flow into you.
(curse shatters)
Nailed it. (giggles)
A kid?
Must've snuck in here to play
but ran into the curse instead.
Hey, it's alright now.
Come on out.
(kid whimpers)
(Nobara sighs)
(clears throat)
Guess he's intimidated
by my beauty.
It happens a lot.
-I'll call Itadori.
-Wait!
Don't leave me here! (screams)
(curse warbling)
(kid screaming)
(curse laughing)
[Nobara] It took him hostage?
This curse has intelligence?
When I say level,
I don't just mean the amount
of cursed energy they have.
It's their cunning.
Monsters that have gained wisdom
will often force cruel
choices upon you.
Where the weight of human
lives hang in the balance.
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
Damn it!
This curse isn't
even all that strong!
Grade 4.
Maybe even less,
like a low grade 3!
(kid whimpers)
But it's aware of that!
That's why it chose
to take a hostage!
Calm yourself down.
If I die, the boy dies, too.
But if he dies, I won't die.
Logically speaking, it's
better if at least I survive.
I mean, right?
I'm unarmed now.
Let the boy go.
(curse laughing)
I'm such an idiot.
It's not letting
go of him at all.
(curse laughing)
Poor Saori, I wish I could've
seen her one last time.
(loud thud)
Huh? I missed?
-(curse warbling)
-(upbeat music)
You okay, bud?
Uh-huh.
(curse warbling)
It's getting away!
No he's not!
-Itadori, give me that arm!
-Huh?
(curse warbling)
-I'll handle it.
-Hold on.
-A straw doll?
-Creepy.
Straw Doll Technique:
Resonance!
(curse warbling)
Oh good.
All right, she's crazy.
We beat it.
(soft piano music)
(truck beeping)
When I was in first grade,
Saori moved to our
village from Tokyo.
Huh?
She was as cute as a doll
and as kind as a nun.
Yet Saori was ostracized
by the villagers.
"She thinks us country
folk are dumb," they said,
they got swept up
in their own paranoia.
And in the end,
they drove her out.
Calling it sickening
wouldn't cover it.
She brought all these homemade
sweets I'd never heard of,
"The ones from the
bakery are even better,"
she'd smile as she
treated me to them.
If I had stayed in
that village, then I...
[Yuuji] This is why I told you!
I said it's dangerous
to go alone
and you need to
take it seriously!
Except you never said it
was dangerous to go alone!
I, wait, I didn't?
And dude, what
have you been eating
that lets you punch through
a wall with your bare hand?
[Yuuji] It wasn't
reinforced concrete!
[Nobara] So?
Most people couldn't
punch through that!
You really don't think so?
You know, you've asked
me a ton of questions
but I've got one for you.
Like why did you
come to Jujutsu Tech?
Why am I here?
Because the countryside sucked!
And I always wanted
to live in Tokyo!
(Yuuji screams)
This was the only
way a poor girl like me
could move to the city
without worrying about money!
You'd risk your life
to save a few bucks?
I would.
Since it means
being true to myself.
(soft music)
If I had stayed in that
village, I'd be as good as dead.
Saori, I made it to Tokyo.
If we ever meet here,
take me to that
bakery you mentioned.
So as far as that goes,
I'm grateful to you, too.
If you hadn't been here,
and he or I had been killed,
the future wouldn't
be so bright.
So thanks.
Well, I guess we've
all got our own reasons
for being here.
Drop it!
I've given you
my thanks already.
We're even now! (giggles)
What is wrong with her?
I live over there!
Thanks again!
Did you know I get into a
bad mood when I'm hangry?
[Yuuji] When are you
not in a bad mood?
[Gojou] Hey there!
Huh?
We made sure the kid got home.
Now how about we grab some food?
-A juicy steak.
-Sushi!
Just leave it all to me!
Megumi, you in?
Huh?
Okay, let's go.
[Nobara] Oh, I forgot about
my biggest haul of the day.
Hey, you, go fetch my things.
[Yuuji] Huh? Why
should I do that?
I thought we were even now.
[Nobara] We won thanks
to my cursed energy.
Got a problem with that?
[Yuuji] What about
my raw strength?
[Nobara] That freak
strength you get
from eating weird shit?
[Yuuji] It's not just from that!
Right, Fushiguro?
Huh? Fushiguro,
what's the matter?
Nothing.
He's pouting 'cause
he didn't get to fight.
Poor little baby.
(Fushiguro grunts)
(Yuuji laughs)
[Kiyokata] Log: July 2018.
West Tokyo City, Eishuu
Juvenile Detention Center.
In the sky above
the exercise yard.
Hey, what is that?
What's what?
[Kiyokata] Unnamed Apparition
of Potential Special Grade.
Its curse womb was witnessed
by several
non-jujutsu sorcerers.
[Teen] That up there!
Looks like an egg.
[Tadashi] What are
you talking about?
[Kiyokata] Due to
its emergency nature,
three Jujutsu Tech first-years
were dispatched to the scene.
And one of them died.
(Closing Theme Music)
[All] Juju Stroll.
[Nobara] I'm going
with paper, Itadori.
[Both] Rock, paper, scissors!
-(Yuuji grunts)
-Yeah!
I guess we can go to
the sushi place in Ginza.
Ginza, yeah!
I want revolving sushi!
(Nobara grunts)
[Nobara] Itadori,
you're such a (grunts),
Fushiguro, say something to him!
If we're going, we should
get something good.
Since Gojou's paying.
Revolving sushi's its own thing,
like how yakisoba and
instant yakisoba are different!
Yeah but I wanna
eat big girl sushi.
[Yuuji] Sushi's a boring meal!
Revolving sushi's an experience!
Like a theme park! Or TDL!
And you said you
were from the country,
so have you ever even been
to a revolving sushi place?
My favorite is Sushi Go,
but I'd go with Splendid
Sushi for a first-timer.
You totally get it!
Hey, cool your jets.
Kugisaki, listen closely.
At Splendid Sushi,
the sushi is delivered
to you on a bullet train.
What?!
Driver, this girl's never
had revolving sushi.
Take us to Splendid Sushi
with the huge-ass parking lot!
(upbeat dramatic music)